caryaudio.com 2010-05-05

# Cary Audio Design - Privacy

This document was last updated November 5, 2008. **  
**

**Introduction**  
Cary Audio Design is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy statement describes our practice with respect to the collection and use of your personal information on this Web site. By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our privacy statement and to Cary Audio Design's processing of personal information for the purposes stated below.

**Contact Information**  
All requests for further information or for permission to reproduce any portions of the materials should be directed to: Cary Audio Design, 1020 Goodworth Drive, Apex, North Carolina 27539, 919-355-0010 (phone), 919-355-0013 (fax).

**Collection**  
Cary Audio Design may ask you to submit personal information at various places on our Web site, including pages for requesting information, joining our newsletter subscription database, or submitting a service warranty registration. The information you voluntarily submit may include, but not be limited to: name, address, phone and email address. We strive to limit our information requests to what we believe is minimally necessary to provide the service you requested.

We use this information to contact you regarding information you have requested or information we feel will be of interest to you. The materials or services may include newsletters, event information, alerts of product updates, special offers, updated information, and other new services from Cary Audio Design. We may also contact you in response to sign-up forms such as 'Contact Us' or 'Warranty Registration.'

Cary Audio Design offers you the opportunity to provide suggestions and contributions by completing a 'Contact Us' form. Please note that any comments or materials sent to us, including feedback data, such as questions, comments, suggestions and any other responses, are deemed to be non-confidential. We have no obligation with respect to such responses, and Cary Audio Design shall be free to use, reproduce, distribute and publicly display such comments and materials without reference to you personally. Cary Audio Design is also free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such responses for any purpose whatsoever.

**Use of Non-Personal Information Collected**  
Cary Audio Design uses non-personal information such as demographic data to analyze and develop marketing strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our products and services, and how to further improve this Web site based upon user data. We may share such non-personal data with third parties.

**Opt-Out**  
Cary Audio Design provides you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive emails from us or updates regarding new services and products offered on this Web site. You may opt out of our email program at anytime by choosing 'Unsubscribe' at the bottom of the last email correspondence you received. You may also opt out by contacting us as info@caryaudio.com. We will process your unsubscribe request as soon as possible, but be aware that this method will take longer to process.

**Third-Party Web Site Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of third-party Web sites. Cary Audio Design makes no recommendations or endorsements about any third-party products or services.

**Changes to the Privacy Statement**  
Cary Audio Design reserves the right to change this privacy statement from time to time. When we do, we will revise the "last update" date at the top of this privacy statement, in which case if you continue to use the Web site, you are agreeing to the amended version of the privacy statement.

**Security**  
We take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. Your privacy is very important to us. However, we do not represent that your personal information is 100 percent safe from security risks associated with personal information.

**Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**  
If you have comments or questions with respect to this statement, please contact us at info@caryaudio.com, or mail to: Cary Audio Design, 1020 Goodworth Drive, Apex, North Carolina 27539, USA, Attention: Marketing. 

|    
---|---
